question_data =[{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"French is an official language in Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A universal set, or a set that contains all sets, exists.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Ottawa is the capital of Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Art","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Leonardo da Vinci was not the creator of the Mona Lisa.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"There is an island in Japan called \u014ckunoshima, A.K.A. &quot;Rabbit Island&quot;, so named because of it&#039;s huge population of rabbits.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]
